<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Malcolm — Software Engineer</title>
    <link>https://www.malcolmmckinney.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Malcolm — Software Engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 19:30:01 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.malcolmmckinney.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Over-The-Counter Class I Medicines</title>
      <link>https://www.malcolmmckinney.com/projects/classonemedicines/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 19:24:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.malcolmmckinney.com/projects/classonemedicines/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2016, there were not many easy and convenient ways to order over-the-counter class one medicines online in Japan. To explain briefly, class one is a special designation of drug, in which a pharmacist must approve the use of before sale.
The general flow is such: if one is experiencing symptoms of disease, he or she would first would go to a doctor to correctly diagnose the issue. The doctor, after performing tests on the patient, would, in turn, present to the patient a script, which would be presented to a pharmacist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Force Quit API</title>
      <link>https://www.malcolmmckinney.com/projects/forcequitapi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 19:24:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.malcolmmckinney.com/projects/forcequitapi/</guid>
      <description>Continuing for about a decade at LINE, after a developer initiated a deployment (build, restart, rsync operation) in error or if said deployment was hanging or stuck (running for several hours with no progress), there was no automated way to force quit the process. In other words, in order for a developer to terminate his or her ongoing build, he or she must contact the Delivery Infrastructure team on Slack and make a request for them to SSH into the machine responsible for deployment (PMC) and kill the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect Authors</title>
      <link>https://www.malcolmmckinney.com/projects/connectauthors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 19:24:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.malcolmmckinney.com/projects/connectauthors/</guid>
      <description>In 2021, one of the pain points my new team I joined was having was that sticker, emoji, and theme creators needed a way to link their accounts for the purpose of giving recommendations to customers.
For example, let&amp;rsquo;s consider the company &amp;lsquo;Sanrio&amp;rsquo; which owns the intellectual property of Hello Kitty, Gudetama, and Peanuts. Whenever someone is interested in Hello Kitty stickers, we may want to also want to recommend to the customer other Sanrio products such as Gudetama.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
